

63

065 853 8055

 \bowtie

thanon@aphithanawat.me

മ്പ്

/in/aphithanawat



Huaikwang, Bangkok

Personal

iii Birth 1/4/1986 (36 y)

Nickname: Hero Nationality: Thai

Religion: None

Marital Status: Single

Military Status : Completed

SKILLS

FullStack

- Flutter
- NestJS
- React
- NodeJS
- MongoDB
- MSSQL
- Firebase

Devops

- Gitlab CI
- Codemagic
- GCP
- AWS
- Docker / VM
- Security
- Network

THANON APHITHANAWAT

FULLSTACK & DEVOPS

ABOUT ME

I'm fullstack developer with low-mid devops, network, cloud system, security and necessary skills. To start the project from zero to the production with only my self.

I have developed several projects with php, javascript and dart.

I'm a big fan of flutter. I have experience with flutter for last 3 year, javascript 5 year and 3 years with php in the past.

EXPERIENCE

Apr 2022 - Current

CPF / Charoen Pokphand Foods

Lead Backend Developer

- Migration mega project cpf import/export system(over 20yr) to nodejs react
- Migration database to oracle
- Meeting with end user for best the solution (user review and discuss) every two day
- Support and guide development team SA, FE, QA, PO (team member
- Cloud service intergration with nodejs (Cloudwatch, S3, grafana, kafka)
- Coaching (unit test, clean code, refactor, and more best practice)
- Database design with SA
- Architecture design, api spec with team
- Lead team as scrum master



Dec 2020 - Mar 2022

SCG / Nexter

Full Stack Developer & Devops

- Develop Dulare Healthcare system only my self
- Feature (CMS like wordpress to manage content mobile and web, Chat/ Video Call ,

Report, urgent case notification, stock management)

Frontend (Client) web / mobile / wear : Flutter

Frontend (CMS) web: Flutter

Backend: Nestjs + Firebase,



Feb 2020 - November 2020

Thairath

Senior Full Stack Developer

- Develop web recruitment system only my self

Frontend Client (For Candidate): NextJS

Frontend CMS (For Department): React

Backend: NodeJS

Portfolio

Dulare Healthcare Solution

SCG (Nexter)

Flutter - NestJS

Recruitment System

Thairath

React - NodeJS

ASSET APPRAISAL

GSB Bank

React - NodeJS

Hotel Smart Hub

Localhub

Flutter - PHP - Python

EDUCATION



Chiang Mai Rajabhat University

Bachelor's degree

Information Technology

Language

Thai

English

Chinese

MY Website



EXPERIENCE

Mar 2019 - Mar 2020

Local Hub (Self business)

Full Stack Developer / CEO

- Develop Smart hotel Software on multiplatform web / android / ios only myself
- Hotel automation from smartphone (auto doorlock, light, A/C)
- Hotel client feature (Booking, Payment, Management, Renter permission, ML)
- OCR: for read passport, id card
- Face Recognition : detect guest face and id is match
- Frontend mobile : Flutter Frontend Web : React
- Backend: Nodejs + Firebase IOT: Python with protocol zigbee
- Payment : 2c2p , paypal



June 2017 - Dec 2018

Freelancer

Software Engineer / Pentest / Malware Developer (Contact)

- Develop software in different languages as assigned with (Flutter, Python, Javascript, PHP)
- Develop Malware by python, autoit, c++, c#
- Project Management (Timeline, QC , People , etc)
- Web pentest



Nov 2012 - Jan 2016

Trinitech co.,ltd

Intelligent Solution Manager < Digital Signage / CCTV >

- Develop CMS for digtal signage by php with my self
- Analyzing costs and sales form market and vendor
- Project Design for client site (Plan, Infrastructure, etc)
- Project Management (Timeline, QC , People , etc)
- Infrastructure Configuration



Oct 2010 – June 2012

Everpure & BL Project

Web developer & IT Support

- Develop ecommerce website by php and javascript with only my self
- SEO, Advert, Graphic Design, Digital Marketing
- Maintenance and troubleshooting of IT hardware
- Installation and Configuration of IT hardware
- Installation and Configuration of CCTV, Digtal Signage system

REFERENCE

Team Member

MR. Wattana Hirunsothorn

SCG (Nexter)

062 545 8887

wattanhi@scg.com

Bangkok Thailand

Friend

Miss. Nuntaporn Yanwachira

SCUBE

092 283 0804

mimi_ntp@live.com

Bangkok Thailand